{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Tennis or Game Court Builders \u0026 Resurfacers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40435/":{"taskOID":40435,"originalTaskOID":40435,"setID":726,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4122,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Surface Wanted","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of sport surface do you want?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6290,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Tennis court","answerDisplayText":"Tennis court","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":977,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Basketball court","answerDisplayText":"Basketball court","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3190,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"In-line skate/hockey","answerDisplayText":"In-line skate/hockey","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1501,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Combination of courts","answerDisplayText":"Combination of courts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4980,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Putting green","answerDisplayText":"Putting green","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4123,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Court Surface","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of court surfacing are you interested in?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2920,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Hard court (asphalt or concrete)","answerDisplayText":"Hard court (asphalt or concrete)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5851,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Soft court (clay, fast dry or grass)","answerDisplayText":"Soft court (clay, fast dry or grass)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1745,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Cushioned court (resilient layer over asphalt or concrete)","answerDisplayText":"Cushioned court (resilient layer over asphalt or concrete)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4809,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Portable","answerDisplayText":"Portable","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3357,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Interlocking tile system","answerDisplayText":"Interlocking tile system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4295,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Not sure","answerDisplayText":"Not sure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4122,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Surface Wanted","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of sport surface do you want?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6290,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Tennis court","answerDisplayText":"Tennis court","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":977,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Basketball court","answerDisplayText":"Basketball court","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3190,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"In-line skate/hockey","answerDisplayText":"In-line skate/hockey","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1501,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Combination of courts","answerDisplayText":"Combination of courts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4980,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Putting green","answerDisplayText":"Putting green","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6290,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Tennis court","answerDisplayText":"Tennis court","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":977,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Basketball court","answerDisplayText":"Basketball court","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3190,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"In-line skate/hockey","answerDisplayText":"In-line skate/hockey","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1501,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Combination of courts","answerDisplayText":"Combination of courts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4980,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Putting green","answerDisplayText":"Putting green","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4123,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Court Surface","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of court surfacing are you interested in?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2920,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Hard court (asphalt or concrete)","answerDisplayText":"Hard court (asphalt or concrete)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5851,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Soft court (clay, fast dry or grass)","answerDisplayText":"Soft court (clay, fast dry or grass)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1745,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Cushioned court (resilient layer over asphalt or concrete)","answerDisplayText":"Cushioned court (resilient layer over asphalt or concrete)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4809,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Portable","answerDisplayText":"Portable","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3357,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Interlocking tile system","answerDisplayText":"Interlocking tile system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4295,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Not sure","answerDisplayText":"Not sure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2920,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Hard court (asphalt or concrete)","answerDisplayText":"Hard court (asphalt or concrete)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5851,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Soft court (clay, fast dry or grass)","answerDisplayText":"Soft court (clay, fast dry or grass)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1745,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Cushioned court (resilient layer over asphalt or concrete)","answerDisplayText":"Cushioned court (resilient layer over asphalt or concrete)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4809,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Portable","answerDisplayText":"Portable","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3357,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Interlocking tile system","answerDisplayText":"Interlocking tile system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4295,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Not sure","answerDisplayText":"Not sure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40435/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40435,"taskName":"Tennis or Game Court - Install or Completely Resurface","taskDescription":"Install or Completely Resurface a Court","xmTaskDescriptor":"Tennis or Game Court Builders \u0026 Resurfacers","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":1003,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Tennis resurfacing sports pave Court","textMessagingName":"Inst Ten Court","rolloverLongDesc":"These firms specialize in planning \u0026 installing tennis courts \u0026 associated accessories. Includes plastic tile courts. Note separate categories for general asphalt or concrete work.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes pavement, decking, paint, posts, nets, etc.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install or Completely Resurface a Court.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Tennis Court Construction \u0026 Resurfacing \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Build or Resurface a Game Court, Costs, Reviews","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":77,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Tennis / Game Court Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Tennis or Game Court - Install or Completely Resurface","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Tennis or Game Court Project","urlName":"Tennis-or-Game-Court-Install-or-Completely-Resurface","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Tennis Court Resurfacing Contractors - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs, Reviews","searchKeywords":"Tennis,resurfacing,sports,pave,Court,Resurface,concrete,courts,paving,Game","emcCategoryOid":-12071,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":726,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false}}